cooltext.com 2017-12-28

# Privacy Policy

|  

  * **Logos** ▼

  * **Fonts**

Login |   
| 

## Cool Text Privacy Policy

Cool Text, and its advertisers and affiliates are deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Below is information outlining our continued support for the responsible management of consumer information. 

**Consumer Information**

During the process of delivering an ad to you, Cool Text does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. However, Cool Text does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). The information collected by Cool Text is used for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring ad effectiveness on behalf of our advertisers. 

In some cases, you may voluntarily provide personal information in response to a specific ad (this ad may ask you to fill out a survey or provide your zip code). If this does occur, Cool Text may collect this information on behalf of an advertiser. This information is used by an advertiser to respond to your request. In addition, Cool Text may combine this information with other users' information and review it in an aggregate form to understand the type of individuals who view a specific type of ad or visit a particular kind of website. 

**Data Collection**

Cool Text, as well as most sites on the Internet, use "cookies" to enhance your experience on the web. Cool Text cannot use these cookies to personally identify you in any way. What are cookies and why do we use them? A cookie is a unique number that is provided to you the first time Cool Text serves you an ad. This unique number, which is stored in a cookie file on your computer, helps Cool Text target ads to you. This cookie can help Cool Text ensure that we don't serve you the same ad multiple times, and help our advertisers understand what you like and don't like about their offerings so that they can cater better to your needs the next time you are interested in their products or services. While we believe that cookies enhance your Internet experience by limiting the number of times you see the same ad and delivering more relevant content to you, they are not required for Cool Text to deliver you an ad. 

If you do not want the benefit of cookies, there is a simple procedure to manually delete your cookies. Please consult your web browser's Help documentation for more information. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

## Generator Categories

Most Popular Animated Black Blue Brown Burning Button Casual Christmas Chrome Dark Distressed Elegant Embossed Fast Festive Fire Flourish Fun Futuristic Girly Glossy Glowing Gold Gradient Gray Green Grunge Hearts Heavy Holiday Horror Hot Ice Medieval Metal Military Neon Old Orange Outline Pink Plain Purple Red Reflection Rounded Science-Fiction Script Shadow Sharp Shiny Silver Small Space Sparkle Stencil Stone Striped Symbol Tan Thin Trippy Valentines Violent White Yellow |   
Live Logo Stream    Contact Us    Link to this Site
